Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
(Returning Pearl)
(Lin, it's the hour of Zi. Leave immediately.)
(Otherwise, you'll also vanish forever.)
What is love in this world...
That it drives souls to devote themselves to life and death?
(Am I dead?)
(Perhaps Heaven pities me)
(and let me have a sweet dream.)
(You saw the wishlist that day)
(and said this was your greatest wish.)
(Jing Yuan,)
(I want to fulfill your wish tonight.)
I'm still alive?
How?
Was it a dream?
Why did it feel so real?
Lord Jing, did you have another sweet dream?
Did you have another sweet dream?
Sui Sui.
You didn't leave.
I'm not leaving.
I'm going to stay
and accompany you forever.
I'm afraid
you'd regret it one day.
Then, just give me lots of love
so I won't regret it forever.
All right?
I promise.
(Returning Pearl)